<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Words on Pippin Barr</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/tags/words/</link><description>Recent content in Words on Pippin Barr</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pippinbarr.github.io/tags/words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Parseltongue? Designing in the Language of Snake</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/05/parseltongue-designing-in-the-language-of-snake/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/05/parseltongue-designing-in-the-language-of-snake/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;No, right?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dead Man in the Bag</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/02/dead-man-in-the-bag/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/02/dead-man-in-the-bag/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://pippinbarr.github.io/images/blog/dead-man-in-the-bag.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/3d/environments/industrial/dead-man-in-the-bag-79484"&gt;Dead Man in the Bag&lt;/a&gt; is a 3D model of a body bag with a body in it. Toes, thighs, stomach, chest, chin, and nose push up the black plastic. A closed zipper across the top makes sure you can&amp;rsquo;t see inside, keeping the the dead man a mystery. He&amp;rsquo;s made of 961 vertices and 4 textures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve never used him in a game, it&amp;rsquo;s not really the sort of thing I go for. I browsed his page many times on the Unity Asset Store, always wanting to buy him but never going through with it. Until I finally did the other day. You can find him in the 3D Industrial category. He&amp;rsquo;s from the 19th of January 2017. In that bag all that time. He has three five star ratings.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>My Evil Twin</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/my-evil-twin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/my-evil-twin/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://pippinbarr.github.io/images/blog/my-evil-twin.png" alt="Hovering the Gemini icon in Google docs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I happened to run into Google&amp;rsquo;s Gemini the other day. I was about to start work on a recommendation letter for an ex-student who was applying for a professor job at a university in Montréal. I was prepping myself to get into that specific kind of writing mode when I saw the little star icon at the top right and hovered it to find out it was Google&amp;rsquo;s AI.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Mouthwashing's lipless mouth</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/mouthwashings-lipless-mouth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/mouthwashings-lipless-mouth/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://pippinbarr.github.io/images/blog/mouthwashings-captain-curly.png" alt="Captain Curly from Mouthwashing lying in the medical bay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rilla and I have been playing &lt;a href="https://www.wrongorgan.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mouthwashing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on and off for the last while. It&amp;rsquo;s not a long game, we just have drifted in and out of consciousness of it. Haven&amp;rsquo;t finished it, but it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a horror-in-space kind of experience, but horror in the more existential senses, no scrambling away from monsters in the ducts (yet). More of the &amp;ldquo;you are the monster in the &lt;em&gt;ducts of your own mind&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; style of horror.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Timpani</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/timpani/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/timpani/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s that thing people write in their blog and then never return again? I feel like Cory Archangel made a project out of it. Someone like that. Anyway, the point is that people start a blog full of determination and wonder at their own bravery, and then quite understandably never return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so it shall probably be with me, though I at least have the sunk cost of about an hour of working with &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/"&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; to try to make it at least somewhat passably useable both in the back end and the front end, so that might give me at least a week of runway? What if I were to add recurring to-dos? What about adding it to my burgeoning habit tracker? How about I make my life miserable as a way to write more? They say the greatest writing comes out of tragedy and sadness, right?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>