<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>book on Pippin Barr</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/tags/book/</link><description>Recent content in book on Pippin Barr</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pippinbarr.github.io/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Stuff Games Are Made Of</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/the-stuff-games-are-made-of/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/the-stuff-games-are-made-of/</guid><description>The Stuff Games Are Made Of by Pippin Barr I wrote a book about experimental game design seen through the perspective of the materials of game creation. There are chapters about everything from computation to user interfaces to time. Check out the the stuff games are made of tag to see the games discussed in the book. All going to plan, the book should be available in the first half of 2023.</description></item><item><title>Les grands classiques de l’horreur en mots cachés</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/les-grands-classiques-de-l-epouvante-en-mots-caches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/les-grands-classiques-de-l-epouvante-en-mots-caches/</guid><description>Les grands classiques de l’horreur en mots cachés by Jonathan Lessard and Pippin Barr Retellings of the stories of *Dracula*, *Frankenstein*, and more in the form of &amp;#34;word find&amp;#34; puzzles. Each chapter of each book is represented as a word find with specific key words plus a secret message at the end! In French. Created with Jonathan Lessard. Links Les grands classiques de l’horreur en mots cachés on the Goélette website</description></item><item><title>How to Play a Video Game</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/how-to-play-a-video-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/books/how-to-play-a-video-game/</guid><description>How To Play a Video Game by Pippin Barr My 2010 book exploring the world of videogames from the perspective of a creative player and asking what makes them so interesting outside the most obvious factors such as engagement, immersion, and so on. Each chapter is a deep dive into a specific idea such as genre, control systems, avatars, and more. Links How To Play a Video Game on the Awa Press website</description></item></channel></rss>