<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Words on Pippin Barr</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/</link><description>Recent content in Words on Pippin Barr</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mouthwashing</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/mouthwashing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/mouthwashing/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="mouthwashings-lipless-mouth-2025-01-23">Mouthwashing&amp;rsquo;s lipless mouth (2025-01-23)&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="./images/mouthwashing.png" alt="Captain Curly from Mouthwashing lying in the medical bay">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Rilla and I have been playing &lt;a href="https://www.wrongorgan.com/">&lt;em>Mouthwashing&lt;/em>&lt;/a> on and off for the last while. It&amp;rsquo;s not a long game, we just have drifted in and out of consciousness of it. Haven&amp;rsquo;t finished it, but it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a horror-in-space kind of experience, but horror in the more existential senses, no scrambling away from monsters in the ducts (yet). More of the &amp;ldquo;you are the monster in the &lt;em>ducts of your own mind&lt;/em>&amp;rdquo; style of horror.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Timpani</title><link>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/timpani/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pippinbarr.github.io/words/2025/01/timpani/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="timpani-2025-01-21">Timpani (2025-01-21)&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>What&amp;rsquo;s that thing people write in their blog and then never return again? I feel like Cory Archangel made a project out of it. Someone like that. Anyway, the point is that people start a blog full of determination and wonder at their own bravery, and then quite understandably never return.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And so it shall probably be with me, though I at least have the sunk cost of about an hour of working with &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/">Hugo&lt;/a> to try to make it at least somewhat passably useable both in the back end and the front end, so that might give me at least a week of runway? What if I were to add recurring to-dos? What about adding it to my burgeoning habit tracker? How about I make my life miserable as a way to write more? They say the greatest writing comes out of tragedy and sadness, right?&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>